A Guide to the Secretary of the Board of Visitors, Office Administrative Files, 1956-1981
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Secretary of the Board of Visitors, Office Administrative Files 1956-1981
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-1/2/1.831
This collection consists of 2000 items.
Administrative Information
Access
For ten years from the date of creation, access to these records will be granted only under the procedures of the Virginia Freedom of Information Act (Code of Virginia -2.1-340 ff.) or with the specific permission of the Secretary of the Board. Researchers interested in obtaining access to these records should direct a request in writing to the Office of the Legal Adviser, Madison Hall, University of Virginia.
Some files in this accession are permanently restricted. Contact Special Collections for details.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1983 June 30.
Scope and Content Information
Office administrative files of the secretary of the Board, including memoranda to the Board and a variety of topical files1956-1981.
Contents List
- Memoranda to Board of Visitors July 1980 - June 1981, 3 folders (Box 1)
- Memoranda to Board of Visitors July 1981 - Dec. 1981 (Box 1)
- Committee on Contractual Relations 1969 Jan. (Box 1)
- Conflict of Interest 1978-1980, 2 folders (Box 1)
- Conflict of Interest 1978-1980, 1 folder (Box 2)
- Mr. Edwin Crawford 1969-1972 (Box 2)
- Faculty Housing 1959-1971, 2 folders (Box 2)
- Faculty Grievance (Restricted) 1969-1970 (Box 2)
- Committee on Future 1972 Sept. - Oct. (Box 2)
- Health, Education, and Welfare 1978 (Box 2)
- Invoices 1980-1981 (Box 2)
- Legal Adviser's Office 1967-1972 (Box 2)
- Dr. William B. Looney (Radiation Safety Officer) 1970-1972 (Box 2)
- Madison Hall 1969-1970 (Box 2)
- Medical Center Relocation (Rector's Correspondence w/Alumni) 1980-1981, 2 folders (Box 3)
- Excerpts from Board Minutes 1974-1981, 2 folders (Box 3)
- Indexing of Minutes 1958-1980, 2 folders (Box 3)
- New Board Members 1954-1964 (Box 3)
- Preliminary Board Meetings 1965-1971 (Box 3)
- Public Affairs' Office 1970-1973 (Box 3)
- Retirement Dinners 1956-1960, 1962, 1963, 1964, 1966, 5 folders (Box 4)
- Self-Study Reports 1981 July-1981 Dec (Box 4)
- Senate Committee 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Senate Finance Committee 1969 Oct-Nov (Box 4)
- Seward Forest 1971-1972 (Box 4)
- Shaner Report 1973 (Box 4)
- Simpson, Grellet C., Chacellor of Mary Washington College 1964-1972 (Box 4)
- Doris K. Wilsdorf (Restricted) 1969-1970 (Box 4)